{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155646587","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155646587"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155663623","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155663623"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155672403","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155672403"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155679745","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155679745"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155686560","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155686560"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155693075","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155693075"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155702502","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155702502"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155712619","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155712619"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155719684","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155719684"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155722656","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155722656"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155732188","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155732188"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155737649","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155737648"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155745514","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155745514"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155751858","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155751857"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155759018","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155759018"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155764028","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155764028"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" b3f11e18-1133-4b1a-a185-6bfe8c0e2ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550155795012","data":{"timestamp":" 1550155795012"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_174704"," gameId":" 4febf0f3-a9a5-4adb-ba70-ac2a5b6c3556"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}